This is a relatively civilized, relatively European,
I have to choose those words carefully too.
Act civilized, act kind.
For the love of God, let me finish a sentence, man.
Maybe you're not used to women talking, I don't know.
Any civilized nation, and yes, Israel is civilized,
compared with some of these other places
around the world.
Do you really think they would surround a hospital?
I wouldn't hear.
But you're a terrorist, you support terrorism.
The moment that this starts becoming chaotic,
like animalistic, we're gone.
If we killed 4,000 Palestinian kids, you know what?
It wasn't enough.
Boom, boom.
That's the first thing we've got to do, isn't it?
Get rid of Hamas and all the nutters out there,
decapitating, lynching their own people,
and bring democracy.
When am I going to get my reparations?
I'm a white woman.
I'm the child of Irish immigrants and British people.
When do I get my reparations from the Roman Empire?
When do I get them from the Vikings?
Which means that you're leading with your bigotry,
your agenda, whether that be your personal agenda
or journalistic.
I can confirm that the president is committed
to rebuilding Gaza and to temporarily relocating
those who are there.
Because as I've showed you repeatedly,
it is a demolition site.
There is no running water.
You won't say this to a Jew.
You won't say this to a Jew, Julia.
You won't talk about Jews in terms of the Holocaust.
You won't talk about the Jews in terms of anti-Semitism.
You won't say to the Jews,
well, you need to get over it.
It was in the past.
You're not the Palestinians, but you know what I mean?
You're a hypocrite.
If you cared about people dying,
if you cared about people dying,
thousands of people dying.
Good evening, Ahmed.
Good evening, infidel.
So you're a terrorist?
Yes, I am a terrorist.
What kind of terrorist?
A terrifying terrorist.